<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kebechet</title>
    <link>https://thoth-station.ninja/kebechet/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kebechet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 13:27:37 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thoth-station.ninja/kebechet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Integrate</title>
      <link>https://thoth-station.ninja/kebechet/how-to-integrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 13:27:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoth-station.ninja/kebechet/how-to-integrate/</guid>
      <description>Three easy steps I will help you to create new releases of your own source code and I will also help you with keeping the depencencies of your source code up to date. Enabling me to work on your source code is easy. It requires hub, which I strongly recommend! As you are a developer yourself, you know the steps by heart:
1 Clone the Source to make changes to my configuration, clone the repositoy: hub clone https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://thoth-station.ninja/kebechet/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 13:18:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoth-station.ninja/kebechet/about/</guid>
      <description>Kebechet  I&amp;rsquo;m Kebechet, goddess of freshness. I will keep your sources and dependencies fresh and up-to-date.
 Kebechet is a SourceOps bot that automates updating dependencies of your project. Currently, it supports managing and updating Python projects based on pipenv files (Pipfile and Pipfile.lock) or requirements.txt/requirements.in files (see pip-tools) - Kebechet is a replacement for it.
Configuration of Kebechet Kebechet is configured using a simple YAML configuration file. Check the documentation of managers to get all the available options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qeb-Hwt</title>
      <link>https://thoth-station.ninja/kebechet/github-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoth-station.ninja/kebechet/github-app/</guid>
      <description>Thoth&amp;rsquo;s GitHub App To use Thoth&amp;rsquo;s GitHub App called Qeb-Hwt, please see our GitHub Marketplace page, just install it to your GitHub user or organization, grant it access to all the repositories (or just a few) and start receiving Pull Request Checks from our Cyborgs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qeb-Hwt GitHub App</title>
      <link>https://thoth-station.ninja/kebechet/github-app-installed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoth-station.ninja/kebechet/github-app-installed/</guid>
      <description>Well done! You have installed and configured Thoth&amp;rsquo;s GitHub App to give advises to Pull Requests opened with the configured Repositories!
Thanks for testing out our pre-release service, feel free to give feedback, have ideas, or raise questions using our GitHub issue tracker.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>